https://lib.usf.edu/copyright/privacy/

Oral History Collections
Protecting our patrons’ personal information is important to us. The USF Libraries adhere to the University of South Florida Internet Privacy Policy and the American Library Association’s Privacy Interpretation of the Library Bill of Rights. Additionally, USF Libraries employs safeguards to protect information collected regarding the use of library services:
Personal information regarding your use of the library website is collected only when you voluntarily provide it directly to the USF Libraries, and then only for its intended purpose
Domain and IP information are collected to facilitate improvements on web services and do not include personally identifiable information
USF Libraries website uses Google Analytics (Google Analytics Security and Privacy Principles)
Library services may employ systems that get updates on current students, staff, and faculty from other university departments, access to this information is restricted to library staff for service purposes only
Records of checkouts and transactions are routinely purged
Personal information is disclosed to contractors or associates only to carry out your requests
Personal information is not disclosed to outside parties, without first obtaining permission from you, unless disclosure is required by law or court order
Contact Us
public All USF Libraries
local_library Ask a Librarian
CopyrightPrivacy
Library Copyright Resources
Copyright & Intellectual Property
Dissertations
Open Access Journals
